

K' Long

C# .NET DEVELOPER

SKILLS

FRONT-END

- HTML, CSS: JAVASCRIPT
- JQUERY, BOOTSTRAP
- ANGULARJS

BACK-END

- NET MVC
- WEB API

OTHER

- GIT
- RESTFUL API
- AZURE

INTERESTS

PROGRAMMING MUSIC

READING

MIDI

GAME

AUDIO MIXING

TECHNOLOGY

8 About me

I am majoring in software engineering.

I have some experiences with C#, ASP.NET MVC, .NET WEB API, Java Android I am interested around MIDI, Audio Processing and Music Producing.

Currently, I am focusing on web development with ASP.NET, ASP.NET CORE and I also have some experience working with this framework.

My goal in the next 3 years is to become a software developer specialized in .NET/.NET CORE framework.

f https://www.facebook.com/longkelvin101099

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/long-kelvin-196a87181/

S live:.cid.a2e714512da2b6f4 https://longkelvin.github.io/

WORK EXPERIENCES

.NET DEVELOPER

8/2021 - 12/2021

ELCA VN



Web application development based on .NET framework

.NET DEVELOPER

1/1/2021 - 30/6/2021

VIHAT TECHNOLOGY CO

Web application development based on .NET framework

EDUCATION -



SOFTWARE ENGINEER

2017 - PRESENT

VNUHCM - UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

PERSONAL PROJECTS

COFFEESHOP_NETMVC

1/3/2022 - 1/8/2022

- https://github.com/LongKelvin/CoffeeShopNetMVC
- C# .NET MVC, ANGULARJS



EZMIDI PIANO

1/9/2020 - 30/7/2021

- https://github.com/LongKelvin/EzMidiPiano
- An Android Music App provide Midi and Synthesizer connection
- JAVA ANDROID, C++ JNI

ASSET MANAGEMENT

2019 - 2020

- C# .NET CORE, ANGULAR 8
- https://github.com/LongKelvin/ASPNET_CORE_QLST
- Asset management for business

MINI SHOP MANAGEMENT APPLICATION

2019 - 2019

- C# WINFORM, SQL SERVER
- https://github.com/LongKelvin/QLST-1
- A small managerment app in C# Winform